Guide to the Shael Shapiro Papers MSS.200
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Architectural Records
  - Job: 7707, 812 Greenwich Street, Judith Brown Loft, 1977; cuid39145 (Box 27, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7744, 812 Greenwich Street, Cameron Loft, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 1-L, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7779, 3 Hanover Square, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Job: 7930, 75 Horatio Street, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 5, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 9)
  - Job: 7318, 28 Howard Street, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Job: 8401, 34 Hubert Street / 250 West Street, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 8011, 55 Hudson Street, 1981 (Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7766, 71 Hudson Street, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 15, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7842, 91 Hudson Street, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Job: 7710, 105 Hudson Street, 1977-1979; cuid39100 (Box 27, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7702, 110 Hudson Street, 1977-1979, 1988-1995, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 9426, 116 Hudson Street, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 9235, 153 Hudson Street, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Job: 9609, 333 Hudson Street, 1997-1998
    - Paper Records, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4, Box 24, Flat-file-folder 7R)
    - Electronic Records, 1997; FA_MSS_200_ER_4
  - Job: 7532, 68 Jane Street, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 9820, 90 John Street, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 1, Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Job: 9817, 59-17 Junction Boulevard, FA_MSS_200_ER_1
  - Job: 7621, 226 Lafayette Street, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Job: 9425, 285 Lafayette Street, old alterations, 1980, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 8920, 295 Lafayette Street, The Puck Building, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Job: 8614, 383 Lafayette Street, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7851, 439-441 Lafayette Street, 1979-1981; cuid40892 (Box 36, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7437, 440 Lafayette Street, 1970-1979 (Box 7, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 7728, 441 Lafayette Street, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Job: 7628, 528-530 LaGuardia Place, 1977-1979; cuid39095 (Box 17, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 7768, 540 LaGuardia Place / 534 West Broadway, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 17, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 9812, 14-22 Leonard Street, undated (Box 12, Folder 7, Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Job: 7906, 81 Leonard Street, 1979-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7818, 55 Liberty Street, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Job: 7715, 120 Liberty Street, 1977-1980; cuid39099 (Box 26, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 4, Box 27, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 8643, 36 Lispenard Street, 1979-1988; cuid40880 (Box 11, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7805, 9-13 Maiden Lane / Job: 7937, 143-149 West 29th Street, 1968-1980 (Box 31, Folder 8-9, Box 26, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 4)
    See also: 74 Broad Street.
  - Job: 7780, 35 Mercer Street, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7208, 53 Mercer Street, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 13, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 8311, 53 Mercer Street, 1982-1987; cuid39226 (Box 1, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7813, 93 Mercer Street, 1978-1982 (Box 35, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7864, 105 Mercer Street, 1971-1981 (Box 23, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7855, 121 Mercer Street, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 9806, 247 Mulberry Street, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Job: 8002, 69 Murray Street, 1980; cuid40873 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 8620, 83 Murray Street, 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 8928, 172 Norfolk Street, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Job: 7919, 20-24 North Moore Street, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 20, Flat-file-folder 6, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 19)
  - Job: 9227, 22 North Moore Street, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 7, Box 40, Folder 10)
    See also: 426-428 Broome Street.
  - Job: 9227, 38-40 North Moore Street, 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5-6, Box 23, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7843, 55 North Moore Street, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7824, 161 Perry Street, 1978 (Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 8409, 161 Perry Street, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Job: 8804, 164-165 Perry Street, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 8625, 165 Perry Street, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 8511, 167 Perry Street, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 2-3, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder TBD 99)
  - Job: 9119, 167 Perry Street, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7714, 101 Prince Street, 1977-1985; cuid39143 (Box 26, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 15, Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Job: 7105, 113-121 Prince Street, Tri-Prince Artists' Coop, 1971-1977; cuid39104 (Box 30, Folder 9, Box 40, Folder 2, 8, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 17)
  - Job: 7432, 123 Prince Street, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 16)
  - Job: 7529, 125 Prince Street, 1975-1985; cuid39091 (Box 15, Folder 9, Box 24, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7857, 125 Prince Street, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 8232, 130 Prince Street, 1983-1984; cuid39081 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7011, 131 Prince Street, 1970-1974; cuid39150 (Box 30, Folder 11, Box 40, Folder 4, Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Job: 7106 / 7008, 133 Prince Street, Prince-Wooster Artists' Coop, 1971-1976; cuid39154 (Box 30, Folder 15, Flat-file-folder 4R, Box 40, Folder 5, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 16)
  - Job: 7418, 141 Prince Street, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7740, 143 Prince Street, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7769, 143 Prince Street, 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 9217, 40 Renwick Street, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7107, 34 Saint Marks Place, East Side Book Store, 1969-1971; cuid39153 (Box 30, Folder 14, Box 40, Folder 6, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 13)
  - Job: 7004, 47 Saint Marks Place, Sobrino Residence, 1970; cuid39148 (Box 30, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 1R, Flat-file-folder 17-R)
  - Job: 7402, 114 Spring Street, 1974-1978; cuid40881 (Box 12, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 7, Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Job: 7411, 115 Spring Street, 1974-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 9R)
  - Job: 8321 / 9307, 118 Spring Street, 1984, 1993-1995; cuid39232 (Box 13, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7440, 122 Spring Street, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Job: 7729, 139 Spring Street, 1978-1988 (Box 28, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7836, 165-169 Spring Street, 1978-1986; cuid40883 (Box 16, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 11, Box 34, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7303, 138 Sullivan Street, 1973-1977; cuid39137 (Box 15, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 8718, 4-12 Thompson Street; 308, 312, 318, 322 West Broadway; and 389 Canal Street, 1988 (Flat-file-folder 21)
  - Job: 9606, 17 Thompson Street, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 17)
  - Job: 8406, 60 Thompson Street, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 4, Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Job: 8640, 90 Thompson Street, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3, Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Job: 0205, 17 Vestry Street, 1985-2001 (Box 19, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 9626, 39-45 Vestry Street, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5-6, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 3, Box 9, Folder 8-9, Box 10, Folder 1-2, Box 1, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 8R)
  - Job: 7928, 427 Washington Street, 1978-1979; cuid39108 (Box 36, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7841, 451 Washington Street, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 8016, 459 Washington Street, 1980; cuid39082 (Flat-file-folder 16)
  - Job: 7770, 465 Washington Street, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Job: 7758, 90 West Broadway, 1979-1987 (Box 24, Folder 20, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 8618, 211 West Broadway, 1980-1992 (Box 7, Folder 11, Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Job: 8542, 285 West Broadway, 1985-1989; cuid39229 (Box 2, Folder 7-8, Flat-file-folder 19)
  - Job: 7202, 307-309 West Broadway, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Job: 7306, 345 West Broadway, 1973-1974; cuid39136 (Box 15, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7936 / 9610, 351 West Broadway, 1980-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 13, Box 39, Folder TBD)
  - Job: 9027, 351 West Broadway, 1985-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 9610 / 9629 351 West Broadway, 1998
    - Paper Records, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10, Box 19, Folder 1, Box 39, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 15)
    - Electronic Records, 1998; FA_MSS_200_ER_2
  - Job: 8316, 382 West Broadway, 1983-1985; cuid39097 (Box 22, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 16, Flat-file-folder 13, Flat-file-folder 14, Flat-file-folder 15, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7862, 383 West Broadway, 1979-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2-3, Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Job: 7524, 392 West Broadway, 1975 (Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 8523 A, 398 West Broadway / 8523 B, 76 Thompson, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 8537, 400 West Broadway, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 13, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 8918, 400 West Broadway, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 8309, 413 West Broadway, 1983-1986 (Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 9028, 421 West Broadway, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7753, 429 West Broadway, 1972-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7427, 431 West Broadway, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 17)
  - Job: 7309, 451 West Broadway, 1973-1978; cuid39090 (Box 15, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7401, 451 West Broadway, John Stern's Loft, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 18, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7120, 451 West Broadway, Showroom for Adel Rootstein, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 7425, 451 West Broadway, 1976 (Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7525, 457-461 West Broadway, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Job: 7603, 465 West Broadway, 1977-1979; cuid39142 (Box 17, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 15, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 8807, 465 West Broadway, 1987-1994 (Box 19, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7746, 471 West Broadway, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7717, 474-478 West Broadway, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Job: 8404 / 8719 / 8903, 475 West Broadway, 1984-1990; cuid39096 (Box 20, Folder 7, Box 21, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 19, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 8943, 475 West Broadway Outdoor Caf, 1984-1990; cuid39228 (Box 1, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 8731, 480 West Broadway, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 9118, 480 West Broadway, 1991; cuid39230 (Box 3, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 8925, 482 West Broadway, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 7904, 12 White Street, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7426, 52 White Street, 1974-1978; cuid40878 (Box 8, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7918, 54 White Street, Teitelbaum Weiss Loft, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 18, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 8719, 60 White Street, 1989 (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7527, 24-26 Wooster Street, undated; cuid39085 (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7612, 39 Wooster Street, undated; cuid40872 (Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7866, 59 Wooster Street, 1979-1983; cuid39111 (Box 38, Folder 2-4, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7871 / 7901 / 8411, 64-68 Wooster Street, 1979-1986 (Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7317, 83 Wooster Street, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 23, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 8205, 84 Wooster Street, 1982-2000 (Box 17, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7438, 97 Wooster Street, 1970-1979 (Box 7, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 8706, 99 Wooster Street, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7921, 101 Wooster Street, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 8708, 102-106 Wooster Street, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Job: 7924, 105-113 Wooster Street, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 6, Box 36, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 8933, 105-111 Wooster Street, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Job: 8402, 114 Wooster Street, 1984 (Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 9234, 115-121 Wooster Street / 433 West Broadway, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7902, 135 Wooster Street, 1971-1979 (Box 33, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 8401, 142 Wooster, 1984 (Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7419, 155 Wooster Street, 1977-1979; cuid39088 (Box 8, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 14, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7630, 7-13 Worth Street, 1977-1978; cuid39139 (Box 17, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 13R, Flat-file-folder 2, Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Job: 7820, 3 York Street, 1978-1985; cuid40888 (Box 35, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7213, City Walls, Frosty Meyers Wall, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 15, Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Department of Buildings documents, various projects, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Design Data, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Job: 9013, Downtown Realty, 1986-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Job: 9017, Eagle Tenants Corp., 1979-1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Job: 7430, Fieldcrest Shop, Copenhagen, undated (Flat-file-folder 10R)
  - Job: 7931, Grooms Loft, undated (Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 10)
  - Job: 7932, Hard Rock Cafe, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Job: 7802, Harley Street Medical Group, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Job: 7835, Keene Chop House, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Job: 8832, Kenin Loft / 140 Thompson Street, 1978-1989 (Box 12, Folder 9-10, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7126, John Lennon and Yoko Ono, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 1, Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Job: 7436, Long Island City Medical and Dental, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7700, Miscellaneous Jobs 1977 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Job: 7800, Miscellaneous Jobs 1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Job: 7900, Miscellaneous Jobs 1979 (Box 33, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 8930 / 8930 A, Olcott Hotel, 1985-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4, Box 39, Folder 6, Box 8, Folder 2-3)
  - Job: 7003, Ordover House, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 6, Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Job: 7601, PS 1 Institute for Art & Urban Resources, 1975-1982; cuid39092 (Box 16, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7320, Plaza Theater, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Professional Liability Insurance Coverage, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Job: 9234, Schur Loft, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 9414, Schur Warehouse, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Job: 7759, Sheer House, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Job: 7420, Smithsonian, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Soho Infill Zoning, undated (Box 19, Folder 7, Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Sweig Residence, Ho-Ho-Kus, New Jersey (Marc Sweig, Architect), 1993 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7201, Tel Aviv Delicatessen, 1972 (Flat-file-folder 19-R)
  - Job: 7743, Tribeca Brochure, undated (Box 25, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 14_r)
  - Job: 7777, Village Voice, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Job: 7856, Whitney Museum, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7203, Wyoming Building, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)